{
    "id": "ba02229b5db347c6977e8121795305f4",
    "title": "If or whether: Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9184ec6401bc41e1acefdc9e8eed9346",
            "title": "If Or Whether",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I am not sure …………………… . I will have the time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whether",
                        "if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She asked me ………………… I was working.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "whether",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We discussed ………………… . we should throw a party to celebrate the occasion.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whether",
                        "if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………… . she will me recognize me I am not sure.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whether",
                        "If",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was a big argument about …………………. she should resign.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whether",
                        "if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can’t decide …………………….. to go on a diet or not.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whether",
                        "if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... she can get along with your mother is another matter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whether",
                        "If",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He asked me ............................................ I had ever been to Europe.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whether",
                        "if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know ....................................... she will come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whether",
                        "if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Janet is going to marry Charles ............................................ she likes it or not.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whether",
                        "if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}